[{"answer": "Well I had I think it was a victory for the fourth amendment, Piers.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "How likely is it this will go to the very top of the legal system in America?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "Well, I think he's been proven right in terms of his views of this program.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "Has Edward Snowden been vindicated by this ruling?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I'm not going to argue against the fact that he brought a lot of things to light.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "ORGAN: How should he have responded then, if he was there reading about all this feeling concerned it breached American's constitutional rights, what else should he have done?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "I would need a lot -- know a lot more about it before I made that type of conclusion, but let's just say that Edward Snowden has shown a light on some of these programs that a great amount of good has resulted from.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "And may I supposed you think if Snowden was to give back the substantial data that he so far not revealed in return for an amnesty would that be a sensible conclusion to this given this court ruling today?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Well, I think that in this case transparency is the way to go.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Why have you done this, and I know that you've read what has not been revealed to the public and you can't talk about the precise detail, but how concern should we be about what we haven't been told?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "I have no comment on Karl or his actions tonight I'm strictly talking about the donations and how our communities come together tonight.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "Do you have any inkling and anything at all, any detail from his past that could possibly explain why this young man would shoot at point blank range Claire Davis who by all account is a delightful young lady, she's a horse lover, very loving family member, why would he even think of doing this?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "Few of the students have teamed up and you're trying to raise money for what purpose?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Claire seems -- she seemed really nice, she had a lot of friends and that she love to ride horses and all that kind of stuff.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "Tell me about Claire, what kind of girl is she?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "I really don't know why Colorado.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "And in terms of Colorado and the number of incidence we've now had in the State Columbine obviously the Aurora tragedy, why do you think this mass shootings and individual shooting incidence, why Colorado?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "You know, I couldn't really say that he was not right or anything.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Did you have any feeling that things weren't quite right with him?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "You know, I couldn't really say.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "Did he ever say stuff in an aggressive way which could explain perhaps some kind of agenda he may have?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "You know, I wasn't in his shoes at the time.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "How on earth does this happen, do you think?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "What else have you been hearing?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Were you aware of any ill will that he bore towards this decision?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "He was a very outgoing person.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "Was there anything in his character would suggest an aggression or an ability to be aggressive?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Words can't describe how I feel for Claire and her family.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "How do you feel about what he did?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "No, sir.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "Did you know Claire?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "This must be a huge shock to everybody, isn't it?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "I haven't actually spoke to the police yet.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "Do you know of other students who can help him?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "Well, there are a couple of important messages that you're previous guest have brought to our attention.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Is there any different or anything else?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "And I would tell you that there are shootings within the black community that we don't cover and that the black community feels necessarily, now that's because the white-run media doesn't care what happens in the black community and I think that they're right.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "We certainly are.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "And we're heading for a very, very big price aren't we?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "That is correct.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "And if there's no winner tomorrow, then the jackpot by Friday could be $800 million which means by this following Tuesday which is Christmas or Christmas Eve, it could be $1 billion, is that right?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "Well, the second side of numbers went down to one and 15.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "So you've made it much more difficult for Americans to actually win this right?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "I am not.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Are you allowed to play, Paula?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Well, I figured Bud used to call it the lottery from hell.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "Is it that it's, you know, that you shouldn't -- be careful what you wish for?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "Well, didn't you have Mike Tyson on here just a little awhile ago and there are folks that by virtue of their character, their limitations, their weaknesses and vulnerabilities, you can put opportunity and money in their world.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "I think the lottery is wonderful.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Is the lottery a force for good or bad in a society like America?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "I'll tell you what.", "docId": "131216pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Are you going to buy a ticket for Mega Millions?", "qSentId": 411}]